[{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678985413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":37515,"timeElapsed":188825},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679030689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":45273,"timeElapsed":234101},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679044183,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":13489,"timeElapsed":247595},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679053950,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":9763,"timeElapsed":257362},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679062376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":8423,"timeElapsed":265787},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679072275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":9896,"timeElapsed":275687},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679079541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":7262,"timeElapsed":282953},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679091225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":11680,"timeElapsed":294637},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679098714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7486,"timeElapsed":302126},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679132848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":28603,"timeElapsed":336260},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679141132,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":8281,"timeElapsed":344543},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679148146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":7011,"timeElapsed":351558},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679157834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9685,"timeElapsed":361246},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679164380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6541,"timeElapsed":367792},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679176498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":12115,"timeElapsed":379910},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679187657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":11155,"timeElapsed":391069},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679200467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":12807,"timeElapsed":403879},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679211780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":11310,"timeElapsed":415191},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679233791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":19760,"timeElapsed":437203},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679249960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":16166,"timeElapsed":453372},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679256549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6586,"timeElapsed":459961},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679262161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5609,"timeElapsed":465573},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679269508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":7344,"timeElapsed":472920},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679280004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":10492,"timeElapsed":483416},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679287028,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":7019,"timeElapsed":490439},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679293718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":6687,"timeElapsed":497130},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679303608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":9887,"timeElapsed":507020},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679356236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":49880,"timeElapsed":559648},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679363898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":7659,"timeElapsed":567310},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679376014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":12112,"timeElapsed":579426},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679398918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":22901,"timeElapsed":602330},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679409333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10412,"timeElapsed":612745},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679415005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":5669,"timeElapsed":618416},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679419827,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4819,"timeElapsed":623239},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679438754,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":18924,"timeElapsed":642166},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679446596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":7838,"timeElapsed":650007},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679464534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":15847,"timeElapsed":667946},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679474121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":9583,"timeElapsed":677533},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679501521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":27397,"timeElapsed":704933},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679505911,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":4386,"timeElapsed":709323},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679511512,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":5598,"timeElapsed":714924},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679518123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":6608,"timeElapsed":721535},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679521503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3377,"timeElapsed":724915},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679526459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4952,"timeElapsed":729871},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679543251,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":16789,"timeElapsed":746662},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679557752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":14499,"timeElapsed":761164},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679570564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":10653,"timeElapsed":773976},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679579880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":9312,"timeElapsed":783292},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679583907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4023,"timeElapsed":787319},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679589902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":5991,"timeElapsed":793313},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679599472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":9567,"timeElapsed":802883},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679604720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5245,"timeElapsed":808131},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679610510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":5788,"timeElapsed":813922},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679621309,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":10796,"timeElapsed":824721},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679631043,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":9732,"timeElapsed":834455},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679653051,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":19879,"timeElapsed":856462},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679658358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5303,"timeElapsed":861770},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679662292,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3931,"timeElapsed":865704},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679666716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4421,"timeElapsed":870128},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679672982,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":6263,"timeElapsed":876394},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679678649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":5664,"timeElapsed":882061},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679683633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4980,"timeElapsed":887045},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679693543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":9906,"timeElapsed":896955},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679701125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":7579,"timeElapsed":904537},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679727885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":24031,"timeElapsed":931297},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679734953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":7065,"timeElapsed":938365},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679746157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":11201,"timeElapsed":949569},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679753734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":7573,"timeElapsed":957146},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679760543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":6804,"timeElapsed":963955},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679770385,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":9839,"timeElapsed":973797},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679777477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":7088,"timeElapsed":980888},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679783226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5746,"timeElapsed":986638},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679789398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":6169,"timeElapsed":992810},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679812306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":20744,"timeElapsed":1015718},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679822311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":10002,"timeElapsed":1025723},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679834944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":12630,"timeElapsed":1038356},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679844344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":9397,"timeElapsed":1047756},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679849199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4851,"timeElapsed":1052610},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679855519,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":6317,"timeElapsed":1058931},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679859293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3770,"timeElapsed":1062705},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679867551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":8255,"timeElapsed":1070963},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679899880,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":32326,"timeElapsed":1103292},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679908042,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":8158,"timeElapsed":1111453},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679920444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":9876,"timeElapsed":1123856},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679931194,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":10747,"timeElapsed":1134606},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679940321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":9124,"timeElapsed":1143733},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679946302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5978,"timeElapsed":1149714},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679955614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":9309,"timeElapsed":1159026},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679963102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":7484,"timeElapsed":1166513},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679967908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4804,"timeElapsed":1171320},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679977252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":9341,"timeElapsed":1180664},{"subjectID":"2kyh20qzv7","prolificID":"6756bd91420aa367a9062639","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b3302b6827a5af08dc9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680002366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":25111,"timeElapsed":1205778}]